

Wilmar Guiling

Hello, I'm Wilmar

I intend to seek a job that would foremost suit my qualification, acquire and contribute experiences not only to myself but also to the company I'll be working with, as well as to discover greater heights of professional growth and development.

CONTACTS



+63 994 4931 076



wilmarch11@gmail.com

EDUCATION

BS in Computer Engineering **Rizal Technological University**

2018 - 2023

Technical Vocational in ICT Senior High School Polytechnic University of the Philippines 2016-2018

Junior High School Carlos L. Albert High School 2012 - 2016

SKILLS

- Programming languages
- Communication
- **Analytical Thinking**
- Troubleshooting
- Attention to detail
- Hardware knowledge

EXPERIENCES:

Internet Cafe Service Technician 2018 - 2020

2 years

Working as a technician in a computer shop provides hands-on experience in technology. It involves diagnosing and resolving hardware and software issues, interacting with customers, and developing technical skills. The role enhances problem-solving abilities and customer service skills, creating a solid foundation for a career in the technology industry.

Payment Associate | ZimiTech Inc. 2020 - 2022

2 years

I find my experience in this field extremely valuable because it has taught me important skills. It has helped me learn how to communicate effectively, even when facing language barriers with my co-workers. It has also taught me the importance of patience and has allowed me to develop strong cooperation and time-management abilities.

RECENT PROJECT

Smart Aquarium: A collaboration of IoT(Internet of Things) and Aquarium

May 2023

The aquarium can be monitored and controlled through a mobile application, utilizing sensors for data collection. Additionally, it incorporates its own filtration system.

School Seminar Certificates:

Title **Date**

- Current Trends in the IT Industry
- Patent information search
- Storage and Cloud Computing
- Data Science
- Wireless Network & Communication
- Best Practices in IT Industries
- Cyber Security and Data Privacy
- Latest Technology in Embedded Systems
- Nanotechnology
- Computer Architecture and Organization

October 17, 2021 October 20, 2021 October 24, 2021 November 7, 2021 November 14, 2021 November 21, 2021 November 28, 2021 December 05, 2021 December 12, 2021 December 12, 2021